#### **EDUCATION**

## Certified Tech Developer,

Professional Developer, Digital House 2022/05 - present | Online It is a career designed and created by Mercado Libre and Globant. It gives the student the technical knowledge and soft skills needed in the IT world.

#### Animations with CSS,

Futuros Tecnologos Globales, Platzi 2022/10

#### Basic JavaScript,

Futuros Tecnologos Globales, Platzi 2022/10

Master degree in Viola Performance, University of North Carolina-School of the Arts 2018/08 - 2020/05 Winston-Salem, United States

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Violin Teacher, Universidad EAFIT 2020/08 - present | Medellin, Colombia I teach individual lessons to people between the age of 5 years old to adults.

#### Violin and Viola Teacher,

Escuela de Musica de Bello 2021/08 - 2022/05 | Bello, Colombia I taught group lessons to groups made of 3 to 10 people.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML-Skillful
- CSS-Skillful
- JavaScript-Skillful
- React-Skillful
- Testing-Skillful

## **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish-Native Spearker
- English-Highly Proficient
- French-B1

# Monica Munoz Alzate

## WEB DEVELOPER



- monicamunozviolin@gmail.com
- +573006420073
- in /monica-mu%C3%B1oz-alzatea49412245/
- /monimunozalzate
- Medellin, Colombia

#### **PROFILE**

I am a Web Developer passionate about the Front-end world. I create experiences for the users working with HTML, CSS, JS and REACT in cross device development with the use of Figma as source of true. I use specialized tools (Jest and Selenium) for testing, covering unit and automated tests. I have knowledge in Back-end using JAVA and MySQL, PYTHON, and also in agile methodologies as Scrum and Kanban.

I consider myself a creative, curious and constantly innovating person. I believe that these qualities are the key to allowing me to come up with effective solutions, and I love the idea of learning by working and putting a lot of attitude into the process.

I started playing violin at the age of 6, which made me a very empathetic, disciplined, resilient, and goal oriented person with a lot of experience working in small and large groups.